{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":720,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":8,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si9851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5183","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9851"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5183"}}},{"id":"si9890","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9878","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9890","si9901","Text_Caption_1","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","Text_Caption_4"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9878"}}},{"id":"si10050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_7","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide9964","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10050","Text_Caption_9","Text_Caption_11","Image_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9964"}}},{"id":"si10645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_15","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide10537","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10645","Text_Caption_15","Image_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10537"}}},{"id":"si10156","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10146q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10183","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10190","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10197","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10205","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10205_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Degree Evaluation\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10220","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10216_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Academic History\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10726","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10722_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Advisor Notes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Student Information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10146q0","for":"Slide10146q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10146q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10146q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10146","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10156","si10183","si10190","si10209","si10220","si10726","si10741","si10250","si10224","si10798"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10146"},"question":{"interactionId":"10170","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Where can you see if a student has any missing requirements?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si10274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10264q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10315","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10327","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10264q1","for":"Slide10264q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10342","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10264q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10355","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10264q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10264","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10274","si10301","si10308","si10327","si10338","si10368","si10342","si10355"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10264"},"question":{"interactionId":"10288","quizId":377,"title":"True/False","text":"The Degree Evaluation includes courses that are in progress and not yet completed?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si10823","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_16","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide10811","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10823","Text_Caption_18","Image_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10811"}}},{"id":"si10891","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10881q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10918","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10925","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10932","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10940","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10944","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10940_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Application Status\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10951","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10955","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10951_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Previous Semesterâ€™s GPA\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11107_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Transcript Totals\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11122","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11126","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11122_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Current Registration\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10881q2","for":"Slide10881q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10959","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10881q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10881q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10881","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10891","si10918","si10925","si10944","si10955","si11111","si11126","si10985","si10959","si10972"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10881"},"question":{"interactionId":"10905","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What area of the Academic History should you compare against the degree evaluation?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"]}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"degreeaudit","class":"project","title":"degreeaudit","children":["Slide5183","Slide9878","Slide9964","Slide10537","Slide10146","Slide10264","Slide10811","Slide10881"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide10146q0","Slide10264q1","Slide10881q2"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5183","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide9878","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide9964","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide10537","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide10146","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide10264","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide10811","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide10881","title":"Slide 8"}]}